https://omf.org/privacy

Privacy Policy - OMF | Missions to East Asia's People
OMF International has a network of websites across the world.
Serve Asia – Short Term Mission
Serving Third Culture Kids (TCKs)
Video Resources
What is a Missionary?
Serve Asia – Short Term Mission
Serving Third Culture Kids (TCKs)
Video Resources
What is a Missionary?
Privacy PolicyHome / Privacy Policy
This notice informs you how we appropriately use and securely handle the personal information you share with us in order that together we may serve the Church and share the Good News of Jesus Christ in all its fullness amongst East Asians.
Your personal information is held and used by us only for OMF International-related purposes. Your data will only be held on systems managed directly by OMF International or our close partners, with appropriate safeguards in place to ensure the security of data, and the limiting of access to only those personnel who have a specific need to access such data. If you have questions, please email webcontact@omfmail.com.
Email communications may be sent to you through the third-party supplier Mailchimp, only using your data in accordance with this notice.The information you provide to register for these email communications will betransferred to MailChimp for processing in accordance with their Privacy Policy and Terms.
You have the right to request us to:
provide you with detail of your personal data that we hold
correct any of your personal data
delete your personal data, subject to any legal or administrative requirements necessitating us retaining that data.
You have the right to complain to your local supervisory authority if you believe that we are using, retaining or securing your personal data inappropriately.
OMF International is a collection of separate centers across multiple countries. You may sign up to receive communications from any of our centers. You may also withdraw your consent at any time. Please be aware that by unsubscribing from communications from one center it will not always unsubscribe you from communications from all other centers.
OMF International2 Cluny Road
Singapore 259570
T +65 6319 4550
OMF International has a network of sites across the world. Select one below.
OMF International's website, like most, uses cookies to help provide you with the best possible experience. Learn moreOkay, thanks
